http://www.signsbytomorrow.com/privacy-policy

PRIVACY POLICY
This Privacy Policy is effective as of January 1, 2020.
Alliance Franchise Brands LLC (“AFB”) and its affiliates, subsidiaries and designees have developed this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) to explain our practices regarding the collection, use, maintenance, protection, disposal and disclosure of information we may obtain from users of our Internet websites located at signsbytomorrow.com, and the related or linked websites of our Centers (as defined in the Terms of Use Agreement) (collectively, the “AFB Sites”) and to comply with applicable laws, rules and regulations.   In this Privacy Policy, AFB or such affiliates, subsidiaries or designees are referred to collectively as “we,” “us,” or “our.”  We believe that our practices allow us to provide great offers to you, without unnecessary use or disclosure of your information. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it.  If you do not agree with our policies, your choice is not to use or access the AFB Sites. By accessing the AFB Sites you agree to this Privacy Policy.
Definitions:
“Cookies” or “Browser Cookies “are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier.  You can instruct your browser to refuse all Cookies or to indicate when a Cookie is being sent.   However, if you do not accept Cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of the AFB Sites.
“Data”, where used in this Privacy Policy, includes Personal Information and Organizational Data.
“Log Files” track actions occurring on the AFB Sites and collect data, including your IP address, browser type, Internet Service Provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.
“Organizational Data” means all non-public information about your business, affairs, customers, suppliers, plans, intentions, market opportunities, operations, processes, product information, including, without limitation, Personal Information received by or through the AFB Sites during the course of our business relationship.
“Non-Personal Information” is defined in Section B below.
“Personal Information” means any information which alone, or in combination with other information, can be used to identify a living person.
Information About you and How We Collect It
We collect several types of information from and about users of the AFB Sites, including information:
Personal Information:
Personal Information might include: (a) contact information (e.g., name, address, phone number, date of birth and email address); (b) credit card information (e.g. credit card number); (c) information regarding your preferences related to us or an AFB Site; (d) information regarding how you became aware of the AFB Sites; (e) business statistics; and/or (f) other personal or business data you provide to us. Personal Information also includes information about your activities, such as Log Files, information about your activity within an AFB Site, and demographic information, gender, geographic area, and preferences, when any of this information is linked to Personal Information that identifies you.
Non-Personal Information
Non-Personal Information is about you but individually does not identify you, such as information about your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our AFB Sites and usage details including IP Address, browser version, system type, page hits, number of visits, web pages viewed and the length of visits to the AFB Sites.
Non-Personal Information is information that we collect about a group or category of products, services, or users that is not personally identifiable or from which individual identities are removed.
Organizational Data
As defined above.
Information You Provide to Us
We collect this information:
Directly from you when you purchase products or services on the AFB Sites, provide feedback on our products or services, request any offer or coupon made available on the AFB Sites, send questions, solicitations, inquires, critiques or comments to us, apply for a job online, or register for specific online programs, surveys, auctions or other transactions or activities. You are not required to provide Personal Information to access an AFB Site.
Information that you provide by filling in forms on our AFB Sites. This includes information provided at the time of registration such as first name, last name, and phone number, and when content is added within the web application. We may also ask you for information when you input a support request, so that we can help to resolve the issue.
Records and copies of your correspondence (including email addresses), if you contact us.
Your search queries on the AFB Sites.
Information We Collect Through Automatic Data Collection Technologies
As you navigate through and interact with our AFB Sites, we may use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions, and patterns, including:
Details of your visits to our AFB Sites, which may include IP Address, traffic data, location data, logs, and other communication data, and the resources that you access and use on the AFB Sites, including Log Files.
Information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, IP Geolocation, operating system, and browser type.
We also may use these technologies to collect information about your online activities over time and across third-party websites or other online services (behavioral tracking). Please email: datagov@alliancefranchisebrands.com for information on how you can opt out of behavioral tracking on AFB Sites and how we respond to web browser signals and other mechanisms that enable consumers to exercise choice about behavioral tracking.
The information we collect automatically is statistical data and may include Personal Information, and Organizational Data or we may maintain it or associate it with Personal Information we collect in other ways or receive from third parties. It helps us to improve our AFB Sites and to deliver a better and more personalized service, including by enabling us to:
Estimate our audience size and usage patterns.
Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our AFB Sites according to your individual interests.
Recognize you when you return to our AFB Sites.
The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include:
Cookies (or browser Cookies). We may collect Non-Personal Information passively using technologies such as Cookies.  We may use Cookies to assign a unique identification to your device which accesses our AFB Sites. Cookies are files that your browser places on your computer's hard drive, which we may use to learn how you arrived at the AFB Sites. Cookies are also used to save and retrieve your e-mail address, password and preferences so you do not have to re-enter this information each time you visit the AFB Sites. In some cases we may track or collect information about your use of the AFB Sites by the numeric address assigned to the computer you are using (your IP address) or by the URLs that you come from or leave to. These methods also allow us to resolve server problems or administer the AFB Sites. You can set your browser to refuse all or some Cookies, or to alert you when Cookies are being sent. To learn how you can manage your Flash cookie settings, visit the Flash player settings page on Adobe's website. If you disable or refuse Cookies, please note that some parts of the AFB Sites may then be inaccessible or not function properly.
Web Beacons. Pages of our the AFB Sites and our e-mails may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs, pixel tags, and single-pixel gifs) that permit AFB, for example, to count users who have visited those pages or opened an email and for other related AFB Sites statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain AFB Sites content and verifying system and server integrity).
We may also collect and store statistics and other Non-Personal information about the online activities of our visitors on an aggregate basis.
For reasons such as improving your experience at our AFB Sites or personalizing our AFB Sites to you (for example, providing better product recommendations or special offers that we think will interest you), we may supplement the information that you provide with information from third parties.
Do Not Track
We do not track users across the web and therefore do not respond to web browser “do not track” signals.
We do not authorize third parties to collect Personal Information from visitors of the AFB Sites for third party use without the visitor’s consent.
Children
The AFB Sites are not intended for children under 17 years of age.  AFB will not knowingly collect any Personal Information from children 17 years of age or younger. When you disclose Personal Information on the AFB Sites, you are representing to us that you are 18 years of age or older. If a person 17 years of age or younger has provided Personal Information to us, a parent or guardian should contact us at datagov@alliancefranchisebrands.com so that we can remove such Personal Information from our active databases.
Using Your Information
Subject to the applicable laws of any relevant jurisdiction(s), we are the sole owners of all information collected on the AFB Sites.  However, we are not in the business of sharing, selling, or renting any information gathered from the AFB Sites.  We will not sell, share or rent the information gathered from the AFB Sites to others in ways that are different from what is disclosed in this Privacy Policy.
We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any Personal Information:
To present the AFB Sites and the contents to you.
To provide you with information, products, or services that you request from us.
To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it.
To provide you with notices about your account, including expiration and renewal notices.
To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection.
To notify you about changes to the AFB Sites or any products or services we offer or provide though it.
To allow you to participate in interactive features on the AFB Sites.
To store data and backup that data.
To track client information and prospective client information for purposes of marketing and accounting.
To collect information about your experience with the application, and to notify us of any delays or interruptions in your experience.
To communicate with you to notify you of actions taken in the system, or when your attention is needed to view or complete an item.
In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.
For any other purpose with your consent.
The Personal Information that you provide will be available to us and our agents, representatives, franchisees and licensees (each an “AFB Party” and collectively, the “AFB Parties” ), as well as AFB’s trusted third-party service providers and contractors (collectively, “Third-Party Providers”).  By submitting Personal Information, you grant to the AFB Parties and the Third-Party Providers a license to use such Personal Information for the purposes described in this section.  The AFB Parties and Third-Party Providers may also use your Personal Information, alone or in combination with the information submitted by other users, to improve the AFB Sites’ navigation or infrastructure, in internal marketing analyses or reviews, and for other administrative purposes.  Additionally, unless you notify us to the contrary, any AFB Party may use your Personal Information in the future to provide you with information on products, services, special offers and/or deals. If you do not wish to receive these types of communications or allow an AFB Party to use your Personal Information in such a manner, please contact us in the manner identified in the "Opt-Out" section below.  Notwithstanding the foregoing, if you are located in Canada, no AFB Party will use your Personal Information to send you information on products, services, special offers and/or deals unless you request to receive such information.
We also might use Non-Personal Information to improve your experience on the AFB Sites and to enhance the AFB Sites. By using the AFB Sites, you grant the AFB Parties and any Third Party Provider a perpetual, irrevocable, worldwide, royalty-free, sublicensable (through multiple tiers) license to use, reproduce, cache, store, modify, publicly perform, publicly display, distribute and transmit such Non-Personal Information for any purpose, and waive any moral rights and publicity rights in such Non-Personal Information.
In all cases, however, any AFB Party or Third-Party Provider that has access to Personal Information or Non-Personal Information is required to use and protect such information in a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy and to use such information only to carry out the activities or services they are performing for you or for us.  Further, we shall limit the information provided to Third-Party Providers to that which is reasonably necessary for them to perform their functions.
Opt-Out
If you choose to opt-out from allowing the AFB Parties to use your Personal Information in the future to provide you with special offers/marketing communications, simply contact us directly at datagov@alliancefranchisebrands.com.  Additionally, “Opt-out” instructions are contained in each special offer/marketing communication sent to you.  Upon receipt and processing of an "opt-out" request, we will, within a commercially reasonable amount of time, remove your information from any listings used to provide you with special offers/marketing communications from AFB Parties in the future. Please note that we may occasionally contact you for administrative purposes even if you unsubscribe from our email list.
Access to, Transfer, Deletion or Amending Personal Information
In accordance with applicable law, you may (i) request access to any Personal Information we hold about you; (ii) request that it be updated, rectified, deleted or blocked; (iii) request that we delete part or all of any Personal Information we hold about you; (iv) request that we restrict our processing of your Personal Information; and (v) request that we provide you or a third party with a copy of certain Personal Information about you (that is referred to as the right of “data portability”).
You may request access to, review, change, or request the deletion of your Personal Information and preferences at any time by contacting us at datagov@alliancefranchisebrands.com. We will then take all reasonable efforts to correct or remove your Personal Information from our active database. We cannot delete your Personal Information except by also deleting your user account. We may not accommodate a request to change Personal Information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the Personal Information to be incorrect.
Data Retention
We will retain your Personal Information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you close your account, we will retain your Personal Information for a period where it is necessary to continue operating our business effectively, to maintain a record of your transactions for reporting purposes until this purpose no longer exists, and to retain as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements.
Your California Privacy Rights
California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits users of our AFB Sites that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of Personal Information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to or write us at: datagov@alliancefranchisebrands.com, or write Alliance Franchise Brands LLC, Attention: Data Governance Committee, 47585 Galleon Drive, Plymouth, Michigan 48170-2466.
Your Canadian Privacy Rights
Your Privacy Rights in Canada may be governed by the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act as amended by the Digital Privacy Act and the Breach of Security Safeguards Regulations as well as the privacy legislation of each Canadian province.  In order to make any inquiry or request, please comply with the second sentence of the immediately preceding paragraph of this Privacy Policy.
Security
We take every reasonable precaution to protect your Personal Information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. Please note, however, that no data security measures can be guaranteed to be completely effective and we cannot guaranty the safety or security of your information.  You understand that your use of the AFB Sites and submission of information to us is at your own risk.
Limits on Our Abilities
Your privacy is very important to us. However, due to the existing legal and technical environment, we cannot ensure that your Personal Information will not be disclosed to third parties in ways not described in this Privacy Policy. For example, we may be forced to disclose Personal Information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. Additionally, we can (and you authorize us to) disclose any Personal Information about you to law enforcement or other government officials that we, in our sole discretion, believe is required: (a) by law; (b) to protect and/or defend our property or other legal rights; and/or (c) to protect the personal safety, or property or other legal rights of others. While we will stipulate that any third parties to whom we are entitled to divulge your Personal Information will respect this Privacy Policy, in any event, we cannot and do not guarantee that all such entities will, in fact, follow the terms of this Privacy Policy. Furthermore, if you provide Personal Information to our franchisees, licensees, co-branding partners or other independently owned and operated Centers, such Personal Information will not be subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy.  In addition, in the event that all or substantially all of our membership interest and/or assets are transferred or sold to another entity, we might transfer Personal Information and Non-Personal Information to the acquiring entity, but shall stipulate that any acquiring entity respect the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy.
Changes to Our Privacy Policy
We use collected information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.  However, we reserve the right to change, modify, amend and/or update this Privacy Policy at any time with or without prior notice in our sole and absolute discretion.  We will post such changes, modifications, amendments and/or updates on this webpage, and, if the changes are significant, a notice will be posted prominently on the AFB Sites, so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.  However, your use of the AFB Sites following any changes, modifications, amendments and/or updates to this Privacy Policy constitutes your unconditional agreement to follow and be bound by this Privacy Policy as so changed, modified, amended and/or updated. You are responsible for reviewing this Privacy Policy each time you use or access the AFB Sites.
Contact Information
AFB has appointed a Data Governance Committee to supervise compliance with this Privacy Policy and the law. Questions regarding this Privacy Policy should be directed to the Data Governance Committee by phone at 1-800-726-9050, or email to datagov@alliancefranchisebrands.com, or write Alliance Franchise Brands LLC, Attention: Data Governance Committee, 47585 Galleon Drive, Plymouth, Michigan 48170-2466. For each, write "Alliance Franchise Brands Privacy Policy" in the subject line.
JOIN OUR MAILING LIST
X I am not a robot
11685 Crossroads Circle, Suite EMiddle River, MD 21220
Tel: 844-957-4467
Fax: 844-957-4467
Quick Links
Business ServicesDesign ServicesCustom Sign PrintingBlogInteractive Signage MapStore LocatorAbout UsContact
Popular Solutions
Indoor Dimensional LetteringDigital SignsFeather BannersIndoor Pole BannersVinyl BannersBanner Frames & StandsOutdoor Pole BannersOutdoor LightboxesLED DisplaysPOP Displays
Site Map | Privacy Policy | FAQ | About Us | Store Locator | Business Services | Design Services | Custom Sign Printing | Blog | Terms of Use | Interactive Signage Map
© 2020 Alliance Franchise Brands LLC. All rights reserved. The trademarks and copyrighted designs contained herein are the property of the respective owners. Signs By Tomorrow® is independently owned and operated. Signs By Tomorrow® Centers may or may not perform or offer to perform electrical and/or installation work. If your local center does offer these products and/or services, it is their responsibility to comply with all state and local licensing and regulation code requirements. Your local Signs By Tomorrow can inform you if they perform this work, and if not can refer you to another qualified entity.
x
